kris-stewart.org 2012-12-18

# Flaunt Network // Your #1 Free Fansite Hosting Since 2009!

The following privacy policy applies to Flaunt.nu and all fansites hosted by Flaunt Network. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at [flaunt.nu@gmail.com](mailto:flaunt.nu@gmail.com). At Flaunt Network, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Flaunt Network sites and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Flaunt Network makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Flaunt Network.  
• Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to Flaunt Network and other sites on the Internet.  
• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: Google Adsense, ValueClick Media and Zype Media.

**Opt-Out Cookie**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml](http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml).

Flaunt Network has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Flaunt Network privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
